

NGUYEN QUANG LONG

CUSTOMER SERVICE

PROFILE

- 0765.708.209
- 🔽 nqlong20995@gmail.com
- 730/13 Lac Long Quan Street, Tan Binh Town.
- Height: 174cm
- Weight: 76kg

SKILLS

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Communication skills, Persuasion skills, ...

CUSTOMER PROBLEM SOLVING

Effective listening

CUSTOMER SERVICE

Customer care

HOBBIES

- -Gym, Swimming
- -Charity activities and blood donation

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Support to improve the foreign medical examination form.

ABOUT ME

I have 4-year experience at hospital for the position of customer service. My strength is sociable, well-care to other people, and I'm willing to learn new things from working environment. Moreover, my 2-year experience at sale and management aspect I would like to maintain because It made me more patient and improve my communication skill, time-management skill, problem-solving skill.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER SERVICE

2019 - 2023

HoanMy CuuLong General Hospital

- · Support sales department to make contracts.
- Greet, serve and advise customer giving the highest standard of customer service at all time
- Develop loyalty with our customers by building relationships through follow-up appointments.
- Introduce health check-up packages and close sales to potential customers to achieve the department's KPI target.
- Deal effectly with customer complaints by liasing with the line manage.
- · Keep in touch and take care of customer.
- · Assist doctors in making medical records.

STORE MANAGEMENT

2017 - 2019

LSG Viet Nam

- Support the telesales department to achieve the target of the day.
- · Solve problems that arise.
- · Follow customer service standard.
- Product management: inventory management, goods rotation Internalization and daily, weekly and monthly inspection management.
- Human resource management: training, monitoring, reporting on activities business activities to ensure the achievement of set goals.
- Achievements: 10 consecutive months achieving 100% KPI (sales the highest revenue reached 250 million VND/month).

EDUCATION

FINANCE AND BANKING

2013 - 2017

University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City

The degree of bachelor

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Proficient in Microsofl Office

Toeic: 450